<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<books>
<book>
    <ISBN>9780762460007</ISBN>
    <title>Composing the Cheese Plate</title>
    <author>Brian Keyser, Leigh Friend</author>
    <buy_online>
      <url>https://www.amazon.com/Composing-Cheese-Plate-Pairings-Inventive/dp/0762460008/ref=tmm_hrd_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&qid=1616349374&sr=8-1:</url>
      <link_text>Amazon</link_text>
    </buy_online>
    <price>$22.00</price>
    <comment>
      These recipes, accompanied by beautiful photography, are unique and elegant 
      while still approachable enough to whip up in your own kitchen.  You'll have 
      a great time learning to cook while taking your cheese plate accompaniments 
      to the next level!
   </comment>
</book>
<book>
    <ISBN>9781452182933</ISBN>
    <title>HOT CHEESE: OVER 50 GOOEY, OOZY, MELTY RECIPES</title>
    <author>Polina Chesnakova</author>
    <buy_online>
      <url>https://www.booklarder.com/books/info/hot-cheese-over-50-gooey-oozy-melty-recipes</url>
      <link_text>Book Larder</link_text>
    </buy_online>
    <price>$19.95</price>
    <comment>
      From classics like fondue and raclette, to elevated fair like bechamel sauce and 
      khachapuri, to tailgate staples like cheesy waffle fries and 'Easy Peasy Poutine', 
      if there is a dish that calls for melting cheese,Polina has riffed on it in this 
      collection of culinary greatest hits.
   </comment>
</book>
<book>
    <ISBN>9781603585064</ISBN>
    <title>Cheese and Culture: A History of Cheese and Its Place in Western Civilization</title>
    <author>Paul Kindstedt</author>
    <buy_online>
      <url>https://www.strandbooks.com/product/9781603585064?title=cheese_and_culture_a_history_of_cheese_and_its_place_in_western_civilization</url>
      <link_text>Strand Books</link_text>
    </buy_online>
    <price>$24.95</price>
    <comment>
      A fascinating exploration of the historical evolution of cheeses and the 
      civilizations that spawned them, from Ancient Mesopotamia to the early 20th 
      century.  Impeccably researched without becoming dense, it's an accessible, 
      engaging, and informative read for anyone who's ever wondered where their food 
      comes from.
   </comment>
</book>
<book>
    <ISBN>9781250063458</ISBN>
    <title>The Book of Cheese: The Essential Guide to Discovering Cheeses You'll Love</title>
    <author>Liz Thorpe</author>
    <buy_online>
      <url>https://www.amazon.com/Book-Cheese-Essential-Discovering-Cheeses/dp/1250063450/ref=sr_1_1?dchild=1&keywords=the+book+of+cheese&qid=1616350636&sr=8-1s</url>
      <link_text>Amazon</link_text>
    </buy_online>
    <price>$40.00</price>
    <comment>
      With its engaging vignettes on regions, producers, and production styles, and 
      innovative 'gateway cheeses' classification framework, this book has supplanted 
      Steve Jenkins' Cheese Primer as the ultimate cheese reference for the 21st century.
   </comment>
</book>
</books> 